RAKESH G



7019028282 | rakeshggowda7019@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/rakesh-g-699497237

Objective

An enthusiastic person looking forward to start my career with an organization which will utilize my skills and abilities. My goal is to get associated, gain further experience, knowledge while enhancing company's performance and reputation and attaining my professional goal.

Experience

• Awto.Ai private limited.

1/12/2022 - 31/01/2023

Business Development executive intern Learn about consumer behaviour, customer relationship, sales and maintain the companies daily transaction account.

Namma Bangalore Foundation.
 Community internship at NGOs.
 Survey on BBMP ward delimitation.

20/06/2022 - 20/07/2022

Projects

 A STUDY ON THE CONSUMER PERCEPTION ABOUT THE BRAND IMAGE OF NANDINI PRODUCTS WITH PARTICULAR REFERENCE TO KOMUL

The study covers the consumer perception and its meaning definition, importance and benefits of the topic, The company's Strengths and weaknesses and areas of development or decline are analyzed. Strategic and operational factors are considered.

Objective Of The Study

- > To find out the factors, which influence the consumer to use the Nandini products.
- > To find out the performance of the products according to their viscosity.

Tools For Data Collection Primary data, Secondary data.

Education

• CMR University
MBA (Marketing and Finance)
CGPA: 7.58

• Sree Cauvery Degree College B.Com 2018-2021

CGPA: 6.4

Sree Cauvery Pu college

2016-2018

PUC

Percentage: 51.33

Skills

- · MS Office
- · Adaptive to different kinds of environment
- · Quick learner
- · Able to take on responsibility and justify them.
- · Social media marketing

Achievements & Awards

- Certificate for appreciation from CMR University. [2022]
- Office Automation Computer Education in Shanthala institution. (10/02/2017)

Interests

- Traveling
- Playing cricket
- · Social network

Languages

- English
- Kannada
- Hindi
- Tamil
- Telugu